A Guide to the Papers of Robert Whitehead, 1923-1932 and n. d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Robert Whitehead 1923-1932 and n. d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
6409-b
This collection consists of 15 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer to the University of Virginia Library on 1974 July 8.
Scope and Content Information
The collection consists entirely of papers from Whitehead's legal office in Lovingston, Nelson Co., Va. Almost half of the papers deal with the collection of unpaid bills by his firms S.B. and Robert Whitehead, and Whitehead and Marshall. The remainder contains legal notices, deeds, depositions given in a divorce suit and a land inheritance suit, receiver's reports, decrees of the Nelson Country Court and orders of the Nelson County Board of Supervisors as well as miscellaneous papers, bills and receipts.
Contents List
- Correspondence concerning account collection by Whitehead's firm 1923-1936, 120 items
- Papers concerning the E. R. Thomas Trust Fund 1925-1933, 15 items
- Notices of Motion of Judgement 1927 & 1931, 6 TD (carbons)
- Correspondence and Legal Documents re: Estate of Henry Bowman 1929, 4 items
- Papers concerning the sale of land in Nelson County, Virginia 1929 & 1932, 9 items
- Deeds and Related Correspondence 1930-1936, 38 items
- Miscellaneous Legal Documents 1930-1936, 17 items
- S. B. Whitehead soliciting votes for Commonwealth Attorney 1931 Sept. 15, 1 ALS
- Transcripts of Testimony given in case of Rebecca and Walter Bruce of Nelson County and William Brown vs. Mary Harvey. 1931, 2 items
- Decrees of the Nelson County. Circuit Court 1931-1932, 41 TD (carbons)
- Bills and Receipts 1931-1936, 8 items
- Miscellaneous Documents of the Circuit Court of Nelson County. 1932-1933, 17 TD (carbons)
- Report of Receivers in the Circuit Court of Nelson County. 1932-1933, 10 TD (carbons)
- Papers concerning the Nelson Coounty Board of Supervisors [1932-1933], 4 items
- Decree of the Court concerning the Eliza G. Horsley Estate n. d., 3 copies